http://www.natureshop.com.au/pages/privacy-policy

Shipping costs vary from $9.20 -$16.50 depending on the value of the purchase
Privacy Statement
Nature Shop Pty. Ltd., ACN 125 982 498 ("Nature Shop","we", "our", or "us") is a supplier of organic and natural food and cosmetic ingredients. We recognise the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected about our customers. For the purposes of this Privacy Statement, the word customers includes visitors to our web sites, subscribers to and users of our services and purchasers of our products.
Where is Nature Shop hosted? Nature Shop's website is hosted on the Shopify Content Delivery Network (CDN)
What personal information do we collect? Personal information is information that can be used to identify a person. In the course of providing our products we may collect detailed information about you and your business'. We usually collect personal information directly from you. Typically this is done at the point of placing an order, by requesting a catalogue or sample, at a trade show or expo, or by entering a competition. We may use "cookies" and "web beacons" to track what you do on our website and what you do with any electronic communications we deliver to your email address. Our Cookies and Web Beacons do not collect any personal information about you and therefore cannot be used to identify you personally. Use of personal informationWe will only use the personal information we have collected from you for the purpose of providing you with the information and products you sought from us. We will not use your personal information for any other purpose without the consent of the provider of that information.
Occasionally you may receive promotional information from us. You may opt out of this communication at any time by clicking unsubscribe.We may collect certain non-personal information to optimise our goods and services including our Web pages for our computer. This non-personal statistical compilation and analysis of information may also be used by us or provided to others for marketing, advertising or research purposes. Disclosure of personal information Nature Shop will not disclose, share, sell, or rent any personal information we hold about you without your consent, except where we may be required by law. Security of personal information Nature Shop employs all reasonable administration, technical, personnel, and physical measures to safeguard your personal information in its possession against loss, theft, and unauthorised use, disclosure, or modification. Any electronic transmission of personal information cannot be guaranteed as totally secure, including the Internet. It is your responsibility to secure the computers you use to access your personal information on our website or emails provided to you. Access to personal information You have the right to access your personal information, subject to the exceptions provided for in the Privacy Act. If you require access to this information please Contact Us. For security reasons proof of identity will be requested.
Links to Other Sites
We provide links to Web sites outside of our web sites, as well as to third party Web sites. The content of these linked sites are not under our control, and we cannot accept responsibility for the conduct of companies linked from our website.
Complaints about privacy Please Contact Us if you have any complaints, concerns, or queries regarding our Privacy Statement. Changes to our privacy statement Nature Shop continually reviews and updates this privacy statement to reflect changes as a result of your feedback, considered good practice, or relevant legislative changes. All changes will be reflected on our website, and it is incumbent on you to regularly check and update yourself with updates to our statement. Credit Card information. Credit card information provided to us is stored in Shopify secure servers. Shopify has its shopping cart hosted on a Level 1 PCI DSS compliant server. Shopify complies with the highest level of Payment Card Industry (PCI) standards
Sign up for our Newsletter
Shop
Natural Dyes
Cleanse
Condition
Moisturise
Treatment
Accessories
© 2020 Nature Shop.
